McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A (Box 18)
  - Arb. Law, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Arb. - Liverpool, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Arb. - Maternity Leave (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Arb. - Plant Removal, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Arb. - Procedures, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Arb. - Public Employment, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Arb. - Public Sector (Box 18, Folder 37)
- A-E (Box 19)
  - Arb. - Security Risks, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Arb. - Senority, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Arb. - Seniority, 1953-1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Arb. - Seniority, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Arb. - Short Courses, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Arb. - Theories, 1903 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Arb. - Theories, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Arb. - Tribunal, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Arbitrators, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy, 1949-1955 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Energy, 1948-1957 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Automation, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Auto Workers, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Besch vs. UAW 6/1/65 Proceedings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Beach vs. UAW 4/21/64 Procedure, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Beach vs. UAW 10/6/66 Proceedings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Beach, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Beach, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Beach, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Beach, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Beach, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Bur. Of Labor - Mgmt., 1960 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Callahan - Decision, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Cartoons (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Case Materials, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Case Study Material, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Church + Dwight, 1956-1965 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Code of ----, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Collyer, Rios + Gardner Denver, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Collyer, Rios + Gardner Denver, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Collyer, Rios + Gardner Denver, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Collyer, Rios + Gardner Denver, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Collyer, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Compulsory Arbitration, 1959-1968 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Contract Language (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Costs of Arbitrations -, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Cox, A, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Dearborn + Teamsters, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Discharge, 1974-1979 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Discipline/ Discharge, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Economic Issues, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - El Kind, A., 1960 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Emergency Bd. Procedures, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Enforcement of No Strike Clauses, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- F-L (Box 20)
  - Fact Finding, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fact-Finding, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fact-Finding, 1949-1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fact-Finding, 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fact-Finding, 1949-1951 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fact-Finding, 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fact-Finding, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fact-Finding - Arb. Process, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fact-Finding - Arb. Process, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - ILA, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Borg. Units - NLRB, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Feteml Leg. For Pub Emp. Borg., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - FMCS (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - FMCS, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - FMCS, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - FMCS, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - NAA, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Fibreboard, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Fleming, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Ford, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Ford Umpire System - Thompson, 1955-1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Gen. Amer. Trans. Corp., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - General Electric 1960 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - GE, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - GE - IUE + IBEW, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - General Motors, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Gibson, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Goldberg, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Gov't Adj. -- Chipping '68, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Guthrie Award - RR Ease, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Guthrie, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Health Care Industry - FMCS, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Hildebrand, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Hines v. Amehor Mute, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Holotnak (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Ind. Union Dept. Study --, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Int'l. Harvester, 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Arbitration, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Int'l Hod Carriers, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Int'l Union of Elect. Workers, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Im Workers Dispute, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - St. Resolution for Settlement, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Kennedy, J., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Kirk + Molotov, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Labor Disputes - Clippings, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Labor Disputes - Clippings, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Labor Law, 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Labor, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Labor Mgmt. - Conference - 1945 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Lab. Mgmt Rel. Act, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Lab. Mgmt Rel. in the Fed Ser. (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Larry, RH, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Leg Hist. on Ecm. Impact, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Lockouts, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- M-P (Box 21)
  - Management Rights, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Manson, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - McClellan Bill, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - McClellan - Letters, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - McDermott, T., 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Mediation Legislation, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Mediation Process, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Mediation Process, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Mediation Process, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Mediation Proposal, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Mediation - Selection + Testing, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mediation - Selection + Testing, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Milk Case, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mock Mediation, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - NAA --, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Nat'l - Lab Rel. Act, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Panel of Arbs, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - New Jersey + Wisc. Campul Arb., 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - New Jersey + Wisconsin Compulsory Arb., 1950-1963 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Wisconsin, 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - NYC News Paper Strike (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - N.Y. Hosp. Act, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - NYS - Act to Amend. Labor Law, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - NYS Bd. Of Med., 1937-1959 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - NYS Bd. Of Med, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - NYS Bd of Med., 1952 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Negotiations, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - No-Raiding Agreement, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Ostrin, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Park An Clinical Hosp., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Pay Board - 1971 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Penna RR Strike - 1960 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Pensions + Call Borg., 1959 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Police, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Pompret, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Pops, G. (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Pres. RR Comm., 1962 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Prisons, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Problems of Proof, 1961-1968 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Problems of Proof (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Problems of Proof, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Public Empes, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Public Employees, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Public Emp's, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Public Employees, 1970-1981 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Public Empls., 1973 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Public Employees, 1963-1973 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Public Employment - Education - Discharge, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Public Employment - Education - Discharge, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Public Sector, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Q-S (Box 22)
  - Quest Imagine, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Arb. Bill, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Cases - 64'-'65, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Railroad Clippings, 1949-1965 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Railroad Commission, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Legislation - 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Strike Legislation - 1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Railroad Strike Legislation - 1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Railroad Work Rules Dispute 1963 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Railroads - 1959 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Railroads - Strike Insurance, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Railroads - Work Rules Comm., 1961 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Railway Labor Act, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Act, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Railway Labor Act, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Railway Labor Act, 1965-1984 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Railway Labor Act, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Raskin, 1963-1966 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Republic Steel, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Research Institute of America, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Revision of Taft-Hartley, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Revision of Taft-Hartley, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Rios, R., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Rios, R., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Roy Robinson Chev (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Ruzicka, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Santa Claus, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Seizure, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Seizure, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Seizure, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Seizure, 1948-1963 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Simkin, Wm., 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Solvay, 1952-1954 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Solvay, 1952-1955 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Southern Railway Co., 1961 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Southern Railway Co., 1960 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Sports, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - State Employees Grievance Machinery, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - State Mediation Agencies, 1961-1968 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - State Mediation Agencies, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - State Med-Bds., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - State Med. Bts., 1959-1965 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - State Public Disputes Laws, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - State Public Employees Logs, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- S-Z (Box 23)
  - Steel Case Studies, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Steel Case, 1951-1955 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1959 Labor Dispute - Steel Industry (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Steel Strike, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Steel - 1960 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Steel Panel Rpt., 1938-1949 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 'A New Look at Arbitration' (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Labor-Personnel Report, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Strike Stats, 1954-1959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - New York State 1963 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Strike Votes, 1951-1955 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey's Anti-Strike Law, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Survey of Arbitration '62, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Act, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - T-H Bills, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - T-H Eisenhower, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - T-H Eisenhower, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - T-H Ives, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Misc. (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Local 174 Teamsters vd. Lucas Flour Company, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Mediation (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Rail Dispute '63, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Rail Dispute '67, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Finality Boards, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Railway Labor-Management Dispute, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Unions Avert Clash for Jurisdiction, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - United Stanford Employees, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Urban, 1958-1964 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Ford v. Urban, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Ford v. Urban, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Ford v. Urban, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - VACA, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Wage Stag Bd. -, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Wage Stabilization Board, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - U.A.W. -and- General Motors, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Michigan Brake Company, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - The Wayward Press (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - UPPU (Papermakers) Local 678, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Wirtz, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Women -, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Misc., 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Legislative and Judicial Treatment of Public Employee Work Stoppages, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Yellow Transit, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Yellow Transit, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- AAA-NAA (Box 24)
  - AAA - Arbitration Journal - Adv. Council, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - AAA Community Dispute Services, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - AAA - Community Dispute Services, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - AAA - Community Dispute Services, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - AAA Community Dispute Services, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - AAA Community Dispute Services, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - AAA Community Dispute Service (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - AAA - Dispute Settlement Grant Research, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - AAA - Dispute Settlement Grant-Stutz, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - AAA General, 1971-1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - AAA - General, 1977-1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - AAA - Lab - Mgmt. Seminar, Buffalo 1975 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - AAA - Nat'l Center for Dispute Settlement, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - AAA Nat'l Med. Adv. Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - AAA - 1977 (Wingspread Conf.) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - AAA - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - American Assembly - 1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - American Assembly Conf., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - American Society for Personnel Admin. Conf., 1976 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Amer. Soc. For Pers. Admin. St. Louis Conf., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Assn. of Labor Mediation Agencies Conf., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Conference - General - 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Federal Sector Grievance/ Arb., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Federal Sector Grievance/ Arb., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Federal Sector Grievance/ Arb., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Health Care Conferences, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - IRRA, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - IRRA, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Int'l. Int. Rel. Assn., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Int'l. Society for Labor Law + Soc. Leg., 1973-1987 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Int'l. Society for Labor Law + Soc. Leg., 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - ISLLSL, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Monroe Co. Grievance Comm. - General, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Monroe Co. Grievance Comm. - General, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Monroe Co. Grievance Comm., 1970 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Monroe Co. Grievance Comm., 1970 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Monroe Co. Grievance Comm., 1970 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - NAA Ann Mntrg '66, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - NAA Ann. Mtg. '70, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Ann Mtng. '71, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - NAA Ann Mtng. '72, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - NAA Ann. Mtng. '73, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - NAA Ann. Mtg. '73, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - NAA Ann. Mtg. '73, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- NAA (Box 25)
  - NAA Ann Mtg. '74, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Ann Mtg. '74, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Ann Mtg. '74, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ann. Mtg '74, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Program '74, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Ann. Mtg. '75, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ann. Mtg. '76, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Ann Mtg. '77, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Ann Mtg. '79, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ann Mtg. '80, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - 1980 Annual Meeting (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Ann. Mtg. '81, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Ann. Mtg. '82, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Ann. Mtg. '83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Ann. Mtg. '84, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Ann. Mtg. '85, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Arb., 1985 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - An. Mtg. '86, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Ann. Mtg. '87, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Ann. Mtg. '88, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - NAA Ann. Mtg. Guest List - General, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Profession Survey '70, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Arbitrator Development '73, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - NAA Archives, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Bd. Of Goo '57, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Bd. Of Gov. '63, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Bd. Of Box '69, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Bd. Of Gov. Bus Mtg. Agenda '70, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Bd. Of Gov. '80 -'81, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Bd. Of Gov '82, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Bd. Of Gov. '83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Bd. Of Gov. '84, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - NAA Bd. Of Gov. '84, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Bd. Of Gov. '85, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Arrangements Comm. ('71), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - NAA (Common) Coop. w/ NLRB (1970) (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Committees - Dev. Of Arb's, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Comm. Dev. Of Now Arb's (1971) (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Comm. Dev. Of Now Arb. (1971) (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - (Spec Common) Dispute Settlement, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - (Spec Common) Dispute Settlement, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- NAA (Box 26)
  - NAA Comm's - Dues Waiver Policy - Spec Common, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - NAA Comm's - Dues Waiver Policy - Spec Common, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - NAA, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - NAA - Committees - Dues Waiver Policy Second Group, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - (Common) Essay Contest, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Comm's Ethics + Grievance, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Executive Comm (1971) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Exec. Comm. 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Comm's - Executive Comm. - 1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Comm. - Executive Comm. - 1971 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - (Common) Foreign Correspondents (1970) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Comm. - Future Directions, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Comm. - Future Directions, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Comm. - Future Direction, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - (Common) Guest Policy (1970) (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - (Common) Intern Training, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - (Common) Law + Legislation, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - (Common) Legal Affairs (1970) (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - (Common) Legal Representation, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Membership Comm. '69-'70, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Comm. - Membership '72, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Comm. - Membership 1976-79, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Membership Comm. '80-'81, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Membership Comm. (1982)-83, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Membership Comm. '84, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Membership Comm. '85-'86, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Comm. - Membership Standards, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Comm. - Nominating Comm. '72, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Comm. - Nominating, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Nominating Comm., 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Comm. - Program, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Comm. - Program, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Comm. - Program, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Comm. - Program, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - (Common) Regional Organization (1977) (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Comm. - Res + Educ., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - (Common) Research + Educ., 1978 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Comm. - Training of Arbs. '74, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - (Common Training of New Arb's., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - (Common) Training of New Arb's., 1965-1970 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - (Common) Training of New Arbs (1970) (Box 26, Folder 41)
- NAA (Box 27)
  - NAA Constitution, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Davey, Harold Corresp., 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Directories, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Edwards, Harm. Speech '82, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ethics File, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Ethics File, 1965-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - (NAA) General - 1940's, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - (NAA) General 1940's, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - (NAA) General 1950 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - (NAA) General 1951 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - (NAA) General - 1952 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - (NA) General - 1953 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - (NAA) General 1954 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - (NAA) General - 1955 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - (NAA) General - 1956 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - (NAA) General 1957 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - (NAA) General 1958 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - (NAA General 1959 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - (NAA) General 1960 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - (NAA) General - 1961 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - (NAA) General - 1962 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - (NAA) General 1963 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - (NAA) General - 1964 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - (NAA) General - 1965 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - NAA General 1966 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - NAA - General, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - (NAA) General 1968 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - (NAA) General 1968 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - (NAA) General - 1969 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - (NAA) General, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - (NAA) General - 1973 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - (NAA) General - 1975 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - NAA General 1975 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - (NAA) General 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - (NAA) General 1980 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - (NAA) General '81, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - (NAA) General '82, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - (NAA) General '83, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - (NAA) General '84, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - (NAA) General '85, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - (NAA) General '86, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Hall, S.C. (Pres.), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Invitation's to Meetings, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Ming-Ithaca '70, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- NAA-Neutral (Box 28)
  - Newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - (NAA) Newsletters, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - NAA Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Pres. - Address - '71, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Pres. Elect - Letters of Congrats, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pres. Elect. - Speech, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings 1971 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings Vol., 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Region 6, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Regional Activities - 1962 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Regional Chairmen 1970 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Regional Meeting 12/6/68, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Regional Meeting on Code of Ethics, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Research + Educ. Foundation, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Seminars, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sites, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Survey, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Survey, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Umpire Vols. - Editorial Bd., 1954-1957 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Umpire Vols. - Editorial Bd., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Umpire Vols. Editorial Bd., 1955 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Umpire Vol. - Mass., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Umpire Vol. - Mass., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Umpire Vol. Mass., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Umpire Vol. - Outlines (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Umpire Vol. - Replies, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Umpire Vol. Rpt., 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Volume '60, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - NAA Volume - '62, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - 'Not Out of Order', 1988 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - '89, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - '90, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - '91, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - '92-'93, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- NYC-NYS (Box 29)
  - NYC Conference (Crestine CB) '65, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - NYC off of Call Borg., 1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - YS Civil Service Grievance Bd., 1955 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - NYS Gov. Common Improper Activities, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NYS Gov. Conf. '68, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - NYS Gov. Conf. '80, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - NYS Off of Emp. Rel. '76 (Wollett Mtg.), 1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - NYS Perb - Conferences - 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - NYS Perb Conferences - 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - NYS Perb Conferences - 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - NYS Perb Conferences - 1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - NYS Perb Conferences - '74, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - NYS Perb, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - NYS PERB - Factfinding - Releases, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - NYS PERB - Fact-finding - Releases, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - NYS PERB - Fact-finding - Releases, 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - NYS PERB = Fact-finding Releases, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - NYS PERB General 1967-71, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - NYS PERB General 1972-76, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 19)